[Disclaimer:
All depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only;
viewer discretion is advised]
[Your Third Series]
Don't forget me.
After dealing with everything here,
I'll be on my way to you.
Whoa. Not drunk, huh?
Look at you.
- Ugh...
- Mm...
We got soaked in the rain.
Go take a shower first.
Let go of me.
Sarmonkey should stay in the monkeys' world.
Do not stick your nose into ours...
Is this how you talk to your senior,
JiJi?
Who even is...
It's you, obviously,
"Ji"ranat.
My name is Jam,
not "Snoop,"
"JiJi," or whatever you just called me.
Please get it right,
or else I will report you
to the authorities.
All you do is tease me.
Is it really that much fun?
Can I do the same to you
so you know how bad it feels?
When did I ever do
anything like that to you?
Hm?
Like this.
Go ahead.
Tease me however you like.
Right now,
I'm but a little chick in your hands.
[Your Third Series]
♫Still feeling lonely? Well, you've got me,♫
♫Keeping you busy every day♫
♫I might not be the one you wanted,♫
♫But give it time, you'll love me anyway♫
♫It's your heart, so it's your choice,♫
♫I won't ever stand in your way♫
♫But when they make you blue,♫
♫Can you please let me take care of you?♫
♫I'm here to love you as myself,
not as a surrogate♫
♫Let me be your safe space
when you need a break♫
♫Who cares if I'm not your first or second?♫
♫At least being your third still counts♫
♫I'm here to love you,
no matter who left you with heartache♫
♫Just let me heal your heart,
lending you my aid♫
♫Have faith and believe in love once more♫
♫'Cause good love is your Lucky Third♫
♫Your Third, can it be me, love?♫
[Your Third Series]
Aren't you gonna put some clothes on first?
I would rather not.
This is fine just the way it is.
Are you sober now?
Yes, from the start.
Aren't you uncomfortable?
You take it off, too.
Are we just going to sleep,
or...
are you going to be mine?
Can I have you?
Jam.
Jam...
Jam!
Jam!!
Jam...
Why is he avoiding me?
Did I go too far last night?
I shouldn't have let my feelings
take hold of me.
Jam...
Juju.
After returning home...
the first order of business
is to call Mr. Sib
and tell him that the mission to
Hunt Down the Teeny-tiny Tiger has failed.
Hello, Mr. Sib.
Mr. Jam.
Perfect timing.
You're back, aren't you?
Yes.
I am calling you to talk about this matter,
and I also have a request.
What is it?
I'm currently in Pak Chong.
How about we talk here?
I also have something
I want to talk to you about.
I'd like you to come support Song.
He's a bit tied up.
No problem.
I will be there right away.
Right.
We just saw each other,
and now we have to be apart again, Juju...
"I love my job."
"I love my job..."
- Oh!
- Oh, good heavens!
Jam...
Song...
Hello.
Hi.
Uh... Are you okay?
Oh...
Are you hurt?
I bumped into you pretty hard...
I am fine.
It was nothing.
Okay.
Let me go get some snacks first.
Oh, snacks...
At the cafe?
Yes.
Well, then...
Let me treat you to them
as an apology.
And where's Sarm?
Well...
"Don't forget me."
"After dealing with everything here,
I'll be on my way to you."
It's okay.
You did your best, Jam.
Let's set that matter aside
and...
talk about what's going on now.
Come with me, then, will you?
I need your help.
Right.
If something is troubling you,
you can share it with me, Song.
Isn't a wedding
supposed to be about just two people?
You see,
the more people we invite,
the busier things get,
and the more problems arise,
with the latest being that
the flower bouquet
the groom needs this evening
has yet to arrive.
Where is it being shipped from?
Switzerland.
Then allow me to check for you and see
if the flower bouquet arrived on the flight.
I will try contacting
the air freight department directly.
Oh.
I'll leave you to it, then.
You handle it.
I'll support you.
Okay.
Thank you.
All done.
They informed us that
they would look into it urgently
and reply via email within half an hour.
Thank you very much, Jam.
Take it easy, Song.
Every solution
has a problem.
The other way around.
Of course.
Let's go.
Jam.
Thank you, Song.
Let's go.
Dad.
Mm.
Hello.
Right.
"This wounded tiger..."
Hmph.
"I will return when I am fine."
So you came back because you're fine now?
Dad,
go easy on me.
Where's the bride of the hour?
And where are the others?
Where did they go?
Namnueng is taking care of tonight's event
at the reception hall.
Song is taking care of the venue.
Sib and PiMai
are taking care of the guests for me.
And Mom?
Is she coming?
It's our daughter's wedding,
for goodness' sake.
There's no way she'd miss it.
Dad, Mom wants you to know that...
Sarm!
I thought you weren't coming back.
I have to be here, don't I?
This is my home, too.
Namnueng.
Wow.
You're on fire!
Like, fabulous!
You're shining brilliantly.
Let me tell you this.
If I put you up against the stars,
you'd outshine all of them.
Enough already.
Get dressed up, will you?
I thought the suit I had tailored
would be collecting dust.
Wait.
Who got fitted for the suit instead of me?
Oh.
It was Sib.
You two are just about the same size.
Gosh, how could you compare me to him?
I am
bigger
and longer
by a mile!
When it comes to this kind of stuff...
Just look at the door.
- There.
- Why?
Mine is this big,
and it can reach that door from here.
The apple doesn't fall far from the tree.
We both have it,
but you're totally outclassed!
Gosh, enough, both of you.
Sarm, get dressed up already.
Come on, the guests are waiting, Sarm.
- Alright.
- Come on.
My eyes must have played tricks on me.
Mr. Sarm is still on Ko Pha-ngan, is he?
So gorgeous.
Thank you.
How could this night go on without me?
I know I'm handsome,
but you don't have to
stare at me so much, do you?
Mm.
He got it from me.
Hm?
And his father.
Oh.
- That's true.
- Mm.
And his older sister.
Yes.
It's three to one. What about it?
Sarm.
Hm?
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
What's gotten into our dad and siblings?
It's probably love.
Get used to it.
Tonight,
you've got plenty more surprises
coming your way.
Sarm.
Don't run off anywhere
after tonight's over, okay?
I've got something to talk to you about.
Don't boss me around.
Why can't I?
There's only one person
who has that power.
Who?
Dad, obviously.
Whoa, incredible.
- My son.
- You heard me.
Yes, of course.
He said it himself.
I'm the one who can boss him around.
Understood?
But I'm your son, too, Dad.
Hey, he's my son, you hear?
- Huh?
- Want to pick a fight?
Hey, but I'm your younger brother.
Want a piece of this?
And he's my brother.
Whoa, and that makes two.
I don't care.
I'm the boss here.
Hey, wait.
You want to talk to him?
About what?
Finding him a beauty queen?
Let me tell you, his partner
must be a badass.
The kind with total devastation, Dad?
That's old news.
Now, it has to be
"with total annihilation."
Clear?
Oh, that's wonderful.
Hey.
Dad, don't tell me
you're finding Sarm a partner,
like how you matched Sib with PiMai?
Oh, these two
love each other,
but they didn't even know it,
alright?
Exactly.
We love each other.
Oh, how about that?
See what I mean?
How about that?
They're hammering it home,
aren't they?
Hammer it home.
Oh, my, that's a good one.
How about that?
Oh, so,
you're playing the role
of a kind-hearted cupid,
aren't you, Mr. Decha?
Hm?
Well then,
I'll head inside.
- Mm.
- Right.
See you there.
Okay.
Wait.
I'm coming with you.
- See you.
- Mm.
- Come on.
- This way.
Let me look at you.
- Whoa.
- Do I look beautiful?
You're as beautiful as an angel,
my daughter.
Come on.
Jam.
Song.
Is everything okay?
All is going well.
Whoa.
You look wonderful, Song.
You're making me blush
with that compliment, Jam.
But...
I still haven't showered.
Is that so, Song?
Please keep this between us.
Okay.
I will keep this a secret
between us.
Thank you.
Oh, Little Jam.
Where are you?
Oh.
Dear Traiphop.
Oh,
Uncle Kraisorn.
Good evening.
You've been gone a long time, haven't you?
How are things?
It's been so long.
You look a lot more buff than before, too.
Whoa...
I wouldn't say that.
What about you, Uncle?
Have you been doing well?
As usual, for an old man.
Oh,
I brought him here for you
to look after.
He's been working at Adisuan Farm
for just over a month.
You're Ning-nong, right?
Yes.
Good evening, Mr. Sarm.
No need to call me "Mr. Sarm."
Just call me by my name.
How did you end up working here?
Uh... I just graduated.
And I noticed that your farm, Mr. Sarm...
Uhh... I mean, Sarm...
You were looking for a vet,
so I quickly applied for that position
because I've been wanting to work here
since I was little.
Whoa...
You know how to talk, huh?
Right.
Okay.
Here.
You can always call me
if you need anything.
Don't hesitate.
Your number.
And don't worry, Uncle.
I'll take care of him.
Whoa.
That puts my mind at ease.
You two get close, okay?
Absolutely.
Feel free to call me whenever.
Thank you, Uncle.
- I have to go now.
- Right.
- Make yourself at home.
- Enjoy yourselves.
Work hard, alright?
Take him as an example.
I heard from the main house
that you're back.
At first, it was quite hard to believe.
But seeing you here with my own eyes...
It's clear that you really are.
I couldn't believe it.
You're safe and sound, aren't you?
You're totally fine?
What do you want to happen to me?
You're right.
I thought you'd be gone...
forever.
This is my home.
Sooner or later,
I'll have to come back here.
There's no place like home, right?
Even Ko Pha-ngan can't beat it.
I've only been away for six months,
so there's a lot to catch up on.
We'll talk later.
I need to go now.
Sure thing.
I'm always available for you.
For Adisuan,
I can do anything.
Oh, Jam.
Have you eaten yet?
I think you should go inside
and grab something.
I am not that hungry.
Even if you're not,
you need to have something,
or else...you won't have the energy.
Thank you, Song.
I'm the one who owes you a thank you.
Without you,
I'd be screwed
right now.
Let's...
work together again sometime.
If Mr. Sib sends for me, I will come.
By the way, the next wedding...
is it yours?
My soulmate hasn't been born yet.
But...
the good old feng shui master told me that
an auspicious ceremony
is coming up soon.
If so, I would come bug you
first thing in the morning.
That's a deal, then.
- Deal.
I'll go check on things at the venue first.
Feel free to enjoy yourself.
I'll handle it myself.
Right, Song.
- See you.
Mr. Sib.
Oh, Jam.
Has everyone checked in okay?
There is Mr. Autthakorn,
Chairman of
the Eastern Agricultural Association,
and Mr. Maekmai.
They have informed Song that
they are on their way.
Aside from them,
all the other guests are here.
Earlier,
some reporters
tried to blend in with the guests
and get up close.
Song let them go,
but an official warning
will be issued to their media outlet.
They were local journalists.
Are there any other
problematic media outlets?
None.
All media outlets are operating
within our established boundaries.
Everything's going well?
Yes, smoothly.
And...
Have you had anything?
The chef informed me that
there is sufficient food.
However, appetizers
and cocktails will need to be
replenished regularly.
What was the question again, Mr. Sib?
Are you alright?
Yes, Chef!
Wait!
I don't think you are.
I've arranged a house for you.
The house number is right here.
I think...I should go home.
Bad idea.
It's already late. It's too risky.
More importantly,
you and I
have something to discuss.
Tomorrow will be the perfect opportunity.
Here.
You can order food
using the number on the back.
And if you need anything else,
simply inform the staff
and tell them to put my name down.
And feel free to call me anytime.
Yes, Mr. Sib.
Mr. Jam.
You've been doing an excellent job.
Go get some rest.
Thank you very much.
Yes, Mr. Sib.
Don't forget to eat.
Mr. Sarm...
You stubborn kid.
Come here.
Here.
Mr. Sarm.
Yes?
I've heard from the main house
about your return.
If necessary,
please let me bring six more housekeepers.
While you were away,
they'd been working at the main house.
Why so many, Auntie?
Are we having a sports day here?
Oh, Mr. Sarm...
I simply want to ask
who you'd like to
take care of the housekeeping here.
Anyone will do, Auntie.
Whoever you think is best.
If so,
I'd like Sak's family
to move into the guest house tonight.
Right.
Auntie.
Mr. Jam is staying in the room.
If he wakes up,
please call me, okay?
Mr. Jam?
Who is he?
This feeling I'm having right now..
I'm scared to define what it is.
Despite that,
something deep inside me tells me that
I can't live without Jam.
He's like air,
something I can't live without,
and I need to breathe every day.
I'll be going now.
What did he mean even by "air"?
This old auntie is confused.
Oh.
Sarm.
Where have you been?
Song.
Both of us could use some distance.
What do you mean?
Oh.
PiMai.
PiMai, this way.
Yoo-hoo.
- Song. Sarm.
- This way.
That's right.
PiMai,
come chat with us.
Mm.
Spending all day with Sib
is just boring.
I know, right?
How are you doing, PiMai?
I'm doing well.
What about you two? Are you doing well?
I'm doing just fine.
But there's someone here,
and I'm not sure how he’s doing.
Sarm...
Are you doing well?
And what about you, PiMai?
How's your shop holding up?
It's doing alright.
Oh!
I made desserts for you two, actually.
Whoa.
Can't wait to try them.
Are you for real?
PiMai.
How about you open your dessert shop here?
I'll buy them all every day.
I'm serious.
Hold your horses, Sarm.
PiMai
is about to open another branch.
It's near his husband's place.
Oh, really?
For real?
Oh.
And...
what about the Chiang Mai branch?
You're
leaving Chiang Mai?
I'll still be in Chiang Mai.
As for expanding,
I just talked to Sib.
We haven't agreed on anything yet.
Aha.
Living there alone,
has anyone tried to hit on you?
I'm just
protective of my little brother, you know.
You live far away, too.
Gosh, Sarm.
There's only one
who's been seeing him, no?
Without fail, right?
Hey.
If he comes to see you
empty-handed,
send him back.
He doesn't come empty-handed, of course.
Recently,
he even offered to be his sponsor,
buying him a mall
so he can open a shop.
- Whoa.
- So over-the-top.
Though I heard
this guy's got quite a mouth on him.
Like he's got
a whole pack of dogs in his mouth.
It's true.
PiMai.
Don't give in so easily, okay?
You need to stay strong, you know?
Understood?
Next time,
he'll know better than to mess with you.
How tough do I have to be, Sarm?
Whoa.
Make sure he learns his lesson.
I'm telling you,
even if he comes crawling on his knees,
begging and pleading,
don't listen to him.
Understood?
Gosh.
You just love stirring him up,
don't you, Sarm?
Let me pray that
everything you wish upon him
comes right back to you.
Sadhu.
Wait.
This kind of thing
will never happen to me.
Hey.
Let's take some photos
to remember this by.
Three, two, one.
Let's go rapid-fire.
What is this?!
Why are you all staring at me?
I don't like this at all.
I've only got one pimple.
I thought it was a boil.
It looked just like one.
- So where have you been these past six months,
- Dad.
huh?
Listen.
Here's the story.
This whole time,
I was just tripping.
But right now,
I'm back.
Good as new.
I'm now 100 percent clean.
From now on,
whatever I've caused,
whatever problems have happened,
whether it's system issues,
financial losses,
or the business going under,
I'll take responsibility.
Oh.
And let me tell you,
I won't take long.
Dad!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for neglecting my work
and being irresponsible.
Dad!
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Dad, I'm really sorry!
Hey.
Yes?
When you vanished
and we couldn't reach you,
do you have any idea
how worried your family was, huh?
Oh, I made everyone worry about me?
I'm sorry, Dad.
Dad...
You've got a pimple, too.
See?
Where?
Here. Let me pop it.
- Oh, wait!
- Mm.
I love you, Dad.
Gosh, you win.
You can go wherever you want.
- Go ahead.
- Oh, Dad.
I've got something for you.
I love you.
Love you.
Gosh, just give me one already.
Right, right, right.
My man.
Hey, my man.
I'm truly grateful to you
for bringing good things into my life.
I really appreciate it. Thank you.
Thank you.
Hey!
Sit down.
What?
I already kissed you all.
There's...
one left.
That one.
- Song. Come here already.
- Don't you dare.
- Stay the hell away.
- Come here, Song.
Don't bring shame to your father's name.
Hm.
Then I won't hold back.
Go.
Nim!
Yes?
I'm on cloud nine.
Mr. Sarm...
Mr. Sarm!
This man is now
right in front of you.
Hey! Get back.
Oh.
Little Jam.
Why did you do that to Little Sarm?
Oh!
This Little Sarm is hurt.
Why cannot I do that?
Wait.
What about us?
What is it?
Let go.
I am going home.
But you're my spouse.
Listen carefully, Mr. Sarm.
If sleeping together means
we have to call each other spouses,
then I probably have
77 of them scattered across the provinces.
You are just
a Pak Chong branch spouse, that is all.
Let go.
Hey.
If that's the case,
divorce them all
and let me be your only one.
I must be your number one.
Nothing less.
Do you understand?
Someone like you
could only be my last choice.
Why is that, you might ask?
Because...
you are not
hot!
Can you give me a second chance?
This time,
just request
whatever position you want.
A spinning back hook kick,
a two-fist strike,
or something else?
Just tell me.
I can do it all.
Let's do it now.
Hey! Stop it.
Wait, wait, wait.
You are insane!
Hey, you...
There will not be a next time.
Do not dare pull that again.
Good or bad, I'm still your spouse!
A spouse, you say?
This is a win-win for both of us.
Ouch!
Little Jam.
Come here.
Hey, you!
Hey.
What?
It hurts.
Oh.
You're hurt...
Where does it hurt, Little Jam?
- It hurts.
- Where?
I'm sorry.
Oh, Little Jam.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean it.
Where does it hurt?
Where does it hurt? Ouch!
Ow.
Little Jam.
Little Jam!
You're gonna do this to me, huh?
Fine!
To all security personnel,
close all the entrances and exits.
Tonight,
no one shall leave.
The cat is about to chase the mouse.
Ready.
Set.
And...
Go!
The annual marathon is about to begin.
Curse you, Sarm.
You're going after God's favorite?
You just live your life,
and I will go back to living mine.
I want you to learn
everything about how things work here
within three months.
♫It seems like something's moving♫
♫What's in my heart isn't too much, but I only♫
♫I only wish you nothing but the best♫
♫Hoping your smile will never fade♫
♫That's all, for I don't wish
to take someone's place♫
♫I'll simply be right here, always within reach♫
♫Like a gentle breeze bringing you peace♫
♫I'll stay right here by your side, always♫
♫I'll stay right here by your side♫
[Your Third Series]